Hello, hello friends, welcome to your
own YouTube channel Crazy Boy Zaroor.
I am your friend Atul Goyal. Today we will talk about
wanting such bread again because the
good momentum that Maithani Chakraborty had given by
tweeting well, was restored around two hundred rupees, he had
this hobby around 200 on murder
and the good meter he has,
according to the pack abs, is seen reaching
from there, 14 balls are set, 650 and is also
reacting, so almost the
last thirty percent, his
question has been done, so which
pattern did you type, is it following you, where should
we take it, if we want to take it, then it is
very important to keep trading and investment organized, where will it take
support that you are registering
and what program can it give, so
first of all let's talk about the weekly chart,
oh right, 36.90 10 11, this,
except for a lot of black tractor, this step 4
subject has also lost a lot  If we talk about
its chart pattern, you will see that it has
always maintained distance around this level.
You can see that here an Islamic
or distance tower has been placed and
it always takes support around this line.
Now look, it has taken
support here or start
working upwards because it has formed around this line. The
bottom of the two lines first
comes around Islam, after that it used to
break, that is why it is said that
now it had returned to this line earlier. The next
time when it came around this line, it took
support on the pack and retail. Next time
again, see which is one here, it has
taken support on this channel. It is
possible that
click on it like before and it may be seen
taking support on the bottom left or
you will see that the entire chart pattern will be
visible to you on this page. On this page also, it
forms two lines, the first line has always provided
resistance on it and when it has
appeared in it,
it has been seen touching the upper line, so this is the entire
chart.  You will see the pattern. Now
we have to talk about this type. If you
try to treat it a little more, then the
entire cloth will be visible from this side. There was a
good consolidation here and as it was done on
Islamic, it was visible with the introduction line.
Now after this, people are visible, so if you
look at it, you can
see the full chart pattern from this side. An
interesting compound is seen happening above Delhi Chat. If you
decide on the action, then
S2 is seen taking support.
A Vishal did not back down,
that people miss you. If you
do one on this laptop, the viewers form
around 594. If you break the service and close
down, then this stock will
appear to be weakening even more. So, as mentioned earlier, it will be
around 574. You can
see it sliding towards the health level of 1052, which
becomes support for you. After that, we will add from
here. If it repeats when
we lead, friends, if you want, it is
quite good. So, the first
distance level of it will be its comeback, so you can see it
above the chart.  You see, we have placed 28 here
and it is clear that you can see
that the stock will take a lot of money, we have
tried to go above it, the new
web-based has not been able to go above it, so the
first distance level will be around 1624
and the bank cross symbol
is very important for withdrawing this money of 600, only then
can the store go above it, click on it,
leave support, four, urologist,
both of these, after that 1628 class, so now if we
talk about the bottom, you will see that the
first level in this is formed around 586,
if it takes this product
and moves upwards, then there is a distance of around 620 to 624
and only
told Jasmine, if it is seen sliding from here
and touches this line, then it can be
seen teaching yoga around 552,
so definitely judge the episode,
first of all, keep it in your chart
so that you know at which level
you have to add the staff and  On which
you have to wash the staff
to remove it or to see the obstacle, then
keep it on the chart, if you are
investing in currency trading then
definitely keep an eye on the lower level by
placing a stop loss of ₹50, your share gets back there,
friends, there can be a lot of selling,
thank you, thank you.